太棒了
All right!
从家里赶到医院花了不到七分钟的时间 我们办到了
Yes! From home to the hospital in seven minutes!
对 最难的部分完成了
Yes. The hard part is truly over.
不 但打起精神来 我们有个不错的开始 对吧
We're off to a great start, aren't we?
我知道我可以很快赶到这里 但这一定是创下了纪录
I knew I'd get here fast, but this has to be a record!
- 你们赶到了   - 嗨
- Oh, you made it!     - Hi.
你们怎么会比我们先到
How the hell did you beat us here?
我们搭计程车 你们是走过来的吗
We took a cab. Did you walk?
不 我们也是搭计程车 但我做过实验…
No, we took a cab too. But I did test runs...
- 嗨   - 嘿 你们赶到了
- Hi.     - Hey, you made it!
好吧 难不成有魔法地道通到这家医院
Okay, is there some kind of magic tunnel to this hospital?
罗斯 你留下来聊天 我要去生孩子了
Ross, you stay here and talk. I'm gonna go have a baby.
好吧 嗨 她是瑞秋·葛林
Okay. Hi, this is Rachel Green.
我是罗斯·盖勒 我们在车上打过电话
I'm Ross Geller. We called from the car.
对 我们为你们准备了双人待产室 所以…
We have a semi-private labor room waiting...
对不起 双人房 我们订了单人房
Oh, whoa! I'm sorry. Semi-private? We asked for a private room.
我知道 不幸地是 我们无法保证一定有单人房
Yes, I see that here. Unfortunately, We can't guarantee a private room.
- 现在单人房都满了   - 真是的 你该早点过来的
- Currently, they're all unavailable.     - Man, if only you'd gotten here sooner.
抱歉 我们只有双人待产室
I'm sorry. Semi-private rooms are all we have.
好吧 等我们一下 罗斯
Okay. Just give us a second. Ross?
什么
Yeah?
- 塞点钱给她   - 我真的相信他们没房间了
- Give her some money.     - I really think they're out of rooms.
他们为大人物保留房间 好吧 如果我是总统呢
They're saving them for important people! What if I was the president?
那么我们麻烦大了 你不知道任何国家的地理位置
We'd be in a lot of trouble. You don't know where any countries are.
好吧
Okay.
你能再帮我们看看吗
Say, would you mind checking again?
有没有我们可以使用的单人待产室
See if any, uh, private rooms may have opened up?
这里是医院
This is a hospital.
好吧 你知道吗 我得说我真的不太喜欢你的语气
You know what? I don't really care for your tone.
这不是市里唯一一家医院 我们没有问题…天啊
This is not the only hospital in the city. We have no problem... Whoa. Oh, gosh!
- 什么    - 是阵痛
- What, what?     - Contraction! Ow! Ow!
- 你们想看看双人待产室吗    - 好吧 看看也无妨
- Like to see a semi-private room?     - Yeah, it couldn't hurt to look.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
你只开了两公分 得等到开十公分才行
You're 2 centimeters dilated. We need to get to 10.
- 那得等上一段时间   - 好吧
- It will be a while.     - Oh, okay.
- 我一小时后再回来帮你检查   - 谢谢
- I'll be back in an hour to check on you.     - Thank you.
- 我猜我们得想办法消磨时间   - 没错
- I guess we have some time to kill.     - Yeah, guess so.
喔 你看
Oh, check these out.
我从来没有这么做过
Never done this before.
对 那看起来很不错
Yeah, well, it looks great.
谢谢 我想我们准备好…
Thank you very much. I think we're ready to...
嗨 我是罗斯 我来帮你们毁了这美好的一天
Hi, I'm Ross. I'm here to ruin this magical day for you.
一点都不会 没关系的 马克·何格 她是我太太茱莉
- Not at all. Marc Horger. My wife, Julie.     - Don't worry about it.
- 嗨 菜莉 她是瑞秋   - 嗨 瑞秋
- Hi, Julie. This is Rachel.     - Oh, hi, Rachel.
- 这是你的第一胎    - 对
- Is this your first?     - It is.
小吉米是我们的第三胎
Well, little Jamie here is our third.
如果你们有问题或需要帮忙 叫我们一声
So if you have any questions, just holler.
- 那真的是太棒了   - 对
- That's so sweet.     - Yeah.
- 我得让你们独处下   - 没关系 我们可以一起来
- Let me give you guys some privacy.     - Nonsense. We're all in this together.
我们愿意跟你们分享每一刻
We are gonna share every moment of this with you.
- 我想我们会非常愉快   - 对
- I think we're gonna have some fun.     - Yeah.
- 我想…好吧   - 笑一个
- Oh, okay, I guess.     - Hey, smile!
- 我不知道…   - 我真的不要…
- No.     - I really don't want any...
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
罗斯 我又开始阵痛了
Oh, Ross. Here comes another contraction.
好吧 深呼吸
Okay, just breathe...
- 甜心 我想我也开始阵痛了   - 天啊
- Oh, honey, I think I'm having one too!     - Oh, my God!
- 你看 来吧   - 不
- Hey, look at this. Here you go!     - Oh, no!
哇 三个小时了 还生不出来
Oh, wow. Three hours and still no baby.
生产的奇迹的确让人很想打瞌睡
Ugh, the miracle of birth sure is a snooze-fest.
- 嘿 你要看看好玩的事吗    - 当然要 什么
- Hey, you wanna see something?     - Sure. What?
好 这一定会很好玩 看我怎么吓钱德
This will be fun. Watch me freak out Chandler.
- 甜心   - 什么
- Honey?     - Yeah?
听着 我一直在想…
Listen, uh, I've been doing some thinking...
我不知道是因为 我们来到这里…
...and I don't know whether it's because we're here...
或是瑞秋要生孩子…
...or Rachel's giving birth...
但我想我们应该试着怀孕
...but, um, I think we should try to have a baby.
好吧
Okay.
你说什么
What's that now?
好吧 我也一直在想那件事 我想我们准备好了
Okay. I've been thinking about it too. I think we're ready.
你在开玩笑吗 你觉得我们准备好要怀孕了
Are you kidding? You think we're ready to have a baby?
这真的很好玩
Oh, this is fun.
你们准备要怀孕了 我的小男孩长大了
You're ready to have a baby? My boy's all grown up!
你说你也准备好了
You said you were ready.
对 我只是想跟你开玩笑 让你用高八度的怪声音说话…
I was screwing with you to get your voice high and weird...
就像我现在一样
...like mine is now!
对 但你不是一直都想要生孩子吗
Yes, but haven't you wanted a kid, like, forever?
好吧 滚开 先生
Okay, just back off, mister!
因为我准备生孩子了
Because I am ready to have a baby.
我只是希望乔伊是孩子的爸
I just want Joey to be the father.
- 什么 你疯了吗    - 就是那样 那就是我的目的
- What? Are you crazy?     - Right there! That's all I wanted!
抱歉 医生坚持拉上布幕做检查
I'm sorry. The doctor insisted on closing the curtain for the exam.
那非常… 真的没关系
Oh, that's very... Really, very, very okay.
茱莉的子宫颈开了七公分 大约是四指宽
Julie's cervix is dilated 7 centimeters. That's about four fingers!
- 医生让我自己摸摸看  - 你摸过瑞秋的子宫颈吗 罗斯
- Doctor let me feel it.     - Have you felt Rachel's?
- 没有…我们不会那么做   - 我们不会那么做
- No, I don't...     - We won't be doing that.
如果你要的话 你可以摸摸瑞秋的 再摸摸我的做比较
Well, you could feel Rachel's, then feel mine to compare.
- 我打扰了你们吗    - 太棒了 谢谢
- Am I interrupting?     - Yes! Thank you!
- 没有   - 待会见
- No, no...     - Later.
- 不 你不能丢下我跟他们独处   - 对不起
- You can't leave me with them.     - Sorry.
不 罗斯 我的孩子没有父亲
No, Ross, Ross? Ross? My child has no father!
我很高兴你来了 可能还要再等一下 你该先打电话来
I'm so glad you're here, but it's gonna be a while. I wish you'd called first.
- 没关系 我待会会再跟你爸来一趟   - 喔 好
- I'm coming back later with your father.     - Oh, good.
- 在孩子出生前我得跟你谈一谈   - 好吧 什么事
- I need to talk to you before the birth.     - Okay. What's up?
我有样东西要给你
I brought something that I want to give you.
假设你真的要它
Assuming, of course, that you want it.
妈 你要我娶你
Ma, you're asking me to marry you?
这是你外婆的订婚戒指 我要你把它送给瑞秋
Your grandma's engagement ring, I want you to give it to Rachel.
- 妈 不 别这样 谢谢你   - 听我说…
- Mom, no. Come on. Thank you...     - Just hear me out...
不 好吗 我们谈过了 我们不会因为她怀孕了就去结婚
No! Okay? We're not getting married because she's pregnant.
说真的 罗斯 她不是你在酒吧泡到就上的女孩
Honestly, this isn't just some girl you picked up in a bar and humped.
孩子应该要有家庭
A child should have a family.
你知道吗 我现在无法思考此事 抱歉
I can't deal with this now. I'm sorry.
考虑一下 如果你不那么做 我会再跟你谈上女孩的事
Think about it. If you don't, I'll talk more about humping.
给我吧
Give me that.
- 嗨 亲爱的   - 谢谢你赶过来
- Hi, dear.     - Hi. Thank you so much for coming.
罗斯 快进来
Ross, get in here!
她把我拖出待产室 问我为什么不跟瑞秋结婚
She dragged me out of the labor room to ask me why I'm not with Rachel.
- 你为什么不跟瑞秋结婚    - 你在开玩笑吗
- Why aren't you with Rachel?     - Are you kidding?
我们不会因为孩子的关系就去办结婚 好吗
We're not gonna be together because we're having a baby.
但看起来你们两个属于彼此
It seems you belong together.
别说了 现在我无法想这件事 我得去等孩子出生
I can't deal with this right now. I have to go have a baby.
对 你是要跟谁生孩子
Right. And with who again?
天啊 他疯了 他为什么不跟瑞秋结婚
He's crazy. Why doesn't he wanna be with Rachel?
我知道
I know.
说真的她是个完美女性 我知道她拒绝了我…
She's like the perfect woman. I know she turned me down...
如果她没有 她想跟我在一起 我会抱着她…
...but if she wanted to be with me, I would take her in my arms and...
我有一阵子没有这样吓你们了吧
I haven't bummed you guys out like this in a while.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 那是谁    - 新来的人
- Who's that?     - New people.
那对恶心夫妇怎么了
What happened to the Disgustingtons?
他们去生孩子了 真不公平 罗斯 是我先来的
They're having their baby. It's not fair, Ross. I got here first!
你离开不久 他们就将她推进产房了
After you left, they wheeled her off.
但她走之前 让我看了一下她的产道
Not before she gave me a nice, juicy shot of little Jamie, crowning away.
抱歉
Wow. Sorry.
新来的人怎么样
So, uh, how are the new people?
他们帮彼此取了很不寻常的绰号
Well, they have some unusual pet names for each other.
包括"坏心死人"跟"病态混蛋"
Including, um, "Evil Bitch" and, uh, "Sick Bastard."
- 天啊 是阵痛   - 是吗 好了 深呼吸
- Oh, gosh, a contraction. Ooh, ow!     - Yeah? Okay, okay. Just breathe.
- 你在看她吗    - 没有
- Are you looking at her?     - No!
- 别看她 病态混蛋   - 甜心 我发誓我没有看她
- Don't look at her, you sick bastard!     - I swear I wasn't looking at her!
她要生了 你喜欢吗 你这病态贱人
She's in labor. You like that, you sick son of a bitch?
我只是…
I'm just gonna...
看吧 那都是你偷看的关系 胖变态
See? It's because you were looking, you fat pervert.
不 我相信没有人在偷看 我们只是需要一点隐私
No, no. I'm sure no one was looking. Just want some privacy.
你想念你的女朋友吗
You miss your girlfriend?
别理他们
Just ignore them.
- 你没事吧    - 没事
- You okay?     - Yeah.
- 罗斯   - 什么
- Ross.     - What?
- 他在偷看我   - 嘿
- He's looking at me.     - Hey!
你想活着看到你的孩子吗
Wanna live to see your baby?
别那样跟我先生说话 你这个白痴混蛋
Don't you talk to my husband like that, you stupid bastard!
天啊 如果你那么想要孩子 去偷一个吧
Oh, good God! If you want a baby so bad, just go steal it!
你是怎么了 你什么时候这么喜欢孩子了
Since when are you so crazy about babies?
我不是喜欢孩子 我是为我们感到疯狂
I'm not crazy about babies. I'm crazy about us.
什么
What?
我们总是说以后要生孩子 不是现在…
We talk about having babies someday, not now...
但我开始认为我们应付得来 我们准备好了
...but I'm starting to think that we can handle it. We're good.
我们真的准备好了
We're really good.
我们准备齐全
We are pretty good.
但你没准备好前 我是不会行动的
But nothing has to happen until you're ready.
或许我现在准备好了
Well, maybe I'm ready now.
我是说是有点可怕 或许没关系
I mean, it's a little scary, but maybe it's right.
什么 才不会没关系 我们才没有准备好要生孩子
It's not right! We're not ready for a kid!
- 什么    - 我是在开玩笑 这一定会很好玩
- What?     - I'm kidding. This is gonna be fun.
我们要试试看吗 我们现在要试吗
So we're gonna try? I mean, we're trying?
我们要试着怀孕
We're trying to get pregnant.
我不想在宝宝面前那么做
I'm not comfortable doing this in front of the babies.
- 你想什么时候开始试    - 好吧 等一下
- So when do you want to start trying?     - All right, hold on a sec.
- 你在算生理周期    - 对
- Period math?     - Yeah.
我们可以从现在开始
Well, we could start trying now.
- 在这里    - 不是这里
- Right here?     - No, not here.
或许吧
Maybe here.
这里很完美 我们得想办法消磨时间 医院里有很多床
We got a lot of time to kill. We're in a building that's full of beds!
而且还很干净
And it's so clean!
加油 你这个笨机器 快点
Come on, you stupid machine! Come on!
- 它吃掉你的钱了吗    - 没有
- Aw, it ate your money?     - No.
- 那么楼下见   - 好吧
- I'll see you downstairs then.     - All right.
好
All right.
我拿到了…
Hey, I got one! I got one!
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
- 上或下    - 下楼 谢谢
- Oh, up or down'?     - Oh. Down, please.
我讨厌抢男人的风头 但可以由我来吗
I hate to be a ball-buster, but can I just do it?
- 麻烦你按上楼   - 没问题
- Could you press up too?     - Sure.
- 我真的很遗憾 我也曾摔断过腿 - 是吗 你怎会摔断腿
- I feel bad. I broke my leg once too.     - How did yours happen?
说来话长 那有点丢脸
It's a long, embarrassing story.
就说那是性爱手册排版上出了点小错误
Let's just say, there was a typographical error with a sex manual.
- 你呢    - 车祸
- How about you?     - Car accident.
- 我猜 有个白痴在打手机 没注意看路  - 对 就是我
- Idiot on a cell not paying attention?     - Yeah. Me.
- 喔 嘿 我的电梯来了   - 好
- Oh, hey, that's me.     - Okay.
我想你是来探病的
Hey, uh, I take it you're just visiting someone.
对
Uh-huh. Yeah.
如果你有时间 想拜访其他人…
Well, um, if you have some time, and you wanna visit someone else...
对 我很乐意
Yeah. I would like that.
- 太棒了 我的房号是…   - 等一下 什么 不 电梯
- Great. I'm in room...     - Wait! What? No! Elevator! No!
你得按下按钮才行
You gotta press the button.
护士说他们要送另一位女人过来
They're bringing in another woman.
她怀孕了吗
Ugh. Is she pregnant yet?
她不需要 她还是能比我更快将孩子生下来
She doesn't need to be. She'll still have the baby before I do.
- 罗斯 我又阵痛了   - 好吧
- Oh, Ross! Another contraction.     - Oh, okay. Here, here.
没错…
That's it.
- 喔 听起来好像很痛   - 没错
- Oh, that sounded like a bad one.     - Yeah, it was.
我的阵痛没有那么厉害 又来了
Mine haven't been so bad. Oh, here comes one now.
真的好痛
Oh, that was a big one.
对不起 你能帮我一下吗 我在找一个断了一条腿的病人
Could you help me'? The patient I'm looking for has a broken leg.
他坐着轮椅 31到35岁 非常迷人
He's in a wheelchair. He's early to mid-30s, very attractive.
- 我知道你在说谁   - 太棒了 他住几号病房
- I know who you're talking about.     - Yay! Great! What room is he in?
对不起 只有医院人员能取得资料
Sorry. That information is restricted.
她跟我是一起的 德瑞克·拉莫瑞医生
She's with me. Dr. Drake Ramoray.
哪个德瑞克医生
Dr. Drake who?
拉莫瑞 那是葡萄牙姓 我们需要他的资料 我是医生
Ramoray. It's Portuguese. We need that information. I'm a doctor.
- 这间医院的医生   - 该死 我们正在浪费宝贵的时问
- At this hospital?     - Damn it! We're losing precious time.
你希望头上沾了这男人的血…
You want this man's blood on your head...
- 是手   - 手上
- Hands.     - Hands.
你必须告诉我我的助理描述的人他住几号病房
It is essential that you tell me what room he is staying in.
他是我的病人 我治疗他很多年了
He's a patient of mine.
- 他住816号病房   - 816 谢谢
- He's in room 816.   -816. Thank you.
- 他叫什么名字    - 别说了
- And what is his name?     - No.
- 我想我们找到一个地方了   - 好吧
- I think we found a place.     - Okay.
- 等一下 你想增加一点气氛吗   - 好
- Wait. Wanna set the mood a little?     - Okay.
- 把灯调暗一点   - 好吧
- We'll dim the lights.     - Okay.
或把它们通通关掉
Or turn them out altogether.
没有精油蜡烛 好吧 就这样吧
Uh, no scented candles. Okay, here. There we go.
好吧 替我消毒 但…没关系
Okay, okay. Making me sterile, but okay.
好 对不起 等一下 我们有保险套吗
Okay. I'm sorry. Oh, wait. Do we have a condom?
对了
Oh, right! Ha, ha.
对 98点6度 你会没事的
Yes, 98.6. You're gonna be fine.
就是这里
Ooh, this is it!
- 就是他   - 太棒了 去找他吧
- That's him!     - Great. Go get him!
等一下 或许你该先进去
Wait a second. Or maybe you could go in first.
他真的不是我喜欢的那一型
He's not really my type.
不是你 是拉莫瑞医生 问他问题 看看他是什么样的人
Not you. Dr. Ramoray. Ask him questions and see what he's like.
- 大家会对医生说出所有事   - 你说他是个好男人
- People tell doctors everything.     - You said he's great.
我认识的男人一开始都很好 最后都成了大混蛋
Guys I meet seem nice at first, then turn out to be big jerks.
- 你的确吸引了一些烂人   - 对 我知道
- You do attract some stinkers.     - I know.
朗医生 我已经等了17个小时
Dr. Long, I've been at this for 17 hours.
三个女人被推进来 又被推出去生下了孩子
Three women have had their babies.
你得给我好消息 我张开了几公分 八 九
Give me good news. How many centimeters am I dilated? Eight? Nine?
- 三公分   - 只有三公分
- Three.     - Just 3?
我才是张开了三公分
I'm dilated 3!
虽然进度有点慢 放心 你做的很好
We are moving along slowly. Don't worry, you're doing great.
- 我马上回来   - 谢谢
- I'll be back soon.     - Thank you.
你知道吗 我不等了 我要把孩子逼出来
I'm not waiting. I'm gonna push this baby out.
我要那么做 三公分 大概是这么大吧
I'm doing it. Three centimeters. That's gotta be like this, right?
- 事实上是这么大   - 愚蠢的度量衡系统
- Actually, it's more like this.     - Oh, stupid metric system.
天啊 我们得直接将你推到产房
We'll take you straight to the delivery room.
喔 我的天啊
Oh, for the love of God!
嗨 我是德瑞克·拉莫瑞医生 我得问你几个例行的问题
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray. I have a few routine questions I need to ask you.
真的吗 一直是威尔斯医生在治疗我
I've been dealing with Dr. Wells.
我是说 我是神经科医生 为了预防万一…
I know. I'm a neurologist. To be safe...
威尔斯医生需要更多相关资料 所以他请我过来
...Dr. Wells wanted a more comprehensive overview. So he sent me.
威尔斯医生是女的
Dr. Wells is a woman.
我是在考你 反应不错
That was a test. Good response.
- 好吧 全名   - 克利夫·伯奈特
- All right. Uh, full name?     - Clifford Burnett.
- 生日   - 1968年11月16日
- Date of birth?     - November 16, 1968.
年龄
Age?
- 你不会用生日自己算吗    - 我是医生 不是数学家
- Can't you figure that out?     - I'm a doctor, not a mathematician.
- 33岁   - 好吧
- I'm 33.     - Okay.
- 已婚吗    - 没有
- And, uh, are you married?     - No.
真的吗 33岁还是单身 你害怕许下承诺
Oh, really? So 33 and single? Would you say you have commitment issues?
所有的问题都是私人问题吗
Are all the questions this personal?
对
Yes.
如果你想知道的话 我是鳏夫
Well, if you must know, I'm a widower.
- 太可怕了 我真的很遗憾   - 对
- Oh, that's terrible. I'm really sorry.     - Yeah.
你会跟女人上了床后不再打电话给她们吗
Do you sleep with women and never call them again?
- 不会   - 太棒了
- No.     - Excellent. Excellent.
最后是 你有奇怪的性癖好吗
And, uh, finally, are you into any weird stuff, you know, sexually?
- 没有   - 答错了
- No!     - Ooh. Wrong answer.
- 还有呢    - 他33岁
- What else? What else?     - Uh, he's 33.
是个鳏夫
A widower.
他似乎是个标准男人 他没有奇怪的性癖好
He seemed like a standup guy. And he's not into anything weird sexually.
菲比要出马了
Enter Pheebs.
- 这个房间是空的   - 好吧 等一下 听我说
- This room's available.     - Okay! Wait, listen to me!
已经有四个女人…
Since I've been waiting, four women...
一共是四个 比我子宫颈张开的公分数还多一个
...one higher than the centimeters I'm dilated...
进来又被推出去生孩子 下个是我 轮到我了 那才公平
...have come and gone with their babies. I'm next. My turn. It's only fair.
如果你再推个女人进来 她又比我早生 我就要告你
If you bring in one more woman who has her baby before me, I will sue you.
不是这家医院 我要告你 我先生是律师
Not this hospital. I'm gonna sue you. My husband is a lawyer.
- 瑞秋   - 你好好处理这件事 甜心
- Uh, Rach?     - You get back on that case, honey!
我想下一位产妇不会太快生
I don't think the next patient is far along.
好吧 把她推进来
Okay. Well, then bring her in.
我的天啊
Qh, my God!
我不敢相信
I can't believe this!
但这是千真万确的
And yet, somehow, it's true.
我是说这太棒了 我们可以指腹为婚
I mean, this is so great. We're gonna be baby buddies!
把你的双腿并拢 别让宝宝听见了
Squeeze your legs together, cover the baby's ears.
- 嗨 甜心   - 嗨 甜心
- Hi, sweetie!     - Hi, sweetheart.
我丈夫希德 你们应该没见过他 罗斯 瑞秋 他是希德
This is my husband, Sid. I don't think you've met. Ross, Rachel, this is Sid.
一年前我在皮肤诊所认识他 还好我长了成人型青春痘
I nabbed him at the dermatologist's. Thank God for adult acne!
我还是不敢相信 我是全世界最幸运的人
I can't believe it. I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
真的吗
Really?
他说什么
What did he say?
你得大声一点 他几乎快聋了
You have to speak loudly, he's almost completely deaf.
- 原来如此   - 那当然
- Oh, there you go.     - Of course he is.
恭喜你们 我不知道你们结婚了
Congratulations. I didn't even know you got married.
- 我们没结婚   - 不 不 我们…
- Oh, no. We didn't.     - No, no, we...
什么
What?
我们只是要一起生下我们的孩子 就那样而已
We're just having this baby together, but, uh, that's all. You know?
为什么
Why?
我们还没到那程度 知道吗 但我们很期持宝宝出生
Uh, we're just not in that place, you know? But we're very excited about this.
那样我就没话说了
Oh. Well, then shut me up.
告诉我该怎么做
Just tell me how.
喔 我又开始阵痛了
Uh-oh. Oh, I feel another one coming.